The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
After the tribulation,
the fog in the Sea of Devils dissipated
and a strange black rain began falling.
Many sects were infected by it.
The Spirit Beasts mutated,
increasing in strength.
They even attacked the sects.
Now,
chaos reigns in the Sea of Devils.
Sect Leader,
you asked for a map of ancient teleportation formations.
I found a place that has one !
It's sold in Lian Mo City.
If I want to return to Zhao,
I have to cross the Sea of Devils.
But this place is huge
and conflicts have been going on for years.
The fastest way to travel
is ancient teleportation formations.
I need to find a map of these formations.
Ma Jinrong\NPoison Devil Palace Disciple\NLate stage Core Formation
Shangguan Cai\NPoison Devil Palace Disciple\NLate stage Core Formation
There really is an Eight-clawed Beast here !
I've been tracking this beast for months.
But my cultivation is too low
to catch this beast.
I will have to bother the two of you.
Of course,
Brother Qiu is only at Middle stage Core Formation.
Just leave the matter of killing this beast to us.
If killing this beast didn't require freshly made poison,
I wouldn't have had to rely on Juniors
with my Nascent Soul cultivation.
Brother Wang,
After swallowing that Nascent Soul, I successfully established mine.
I don't know if you've succeeded.
But if you haven't,
when we meet again,
I will have to pay you back.
After you finish the poison and kill this beast,
I'll kill you both.
Huh ? I have met an old friend.
Go !
Impossible...
Such a powerful Divine Sense...
Could it be a monster of the Soul Formation level ?
I've been looking for you.
Long time no see.
Does Senior know me ?
It's you !
Brother Qiu is really in a good mood.
With your Nascent Soul cultivation,
you're playing around with 2 Juniors...
Very interesting.
He's Nascent Soul ?
If we didn't give the beast to him,
he would've certainly killed us !
Thank you for your guidance Senior.
Leaving ?
These two juniors seem to be
from the Poison Devil Palace.
That sect takes good care of their disciples.
Brother Qiu,
you have to be careful in the future.
That guy is a core disciple of the Poison Devil Palace
If he really runs away,
I will have problems in the future
This guy...
With their Late stage Core Formation speed,
if Brother Qiu quickly chases after them,
you might still catch up.
Brother Wang,
say what's on your mind.
Although our relation isn't deep
we still have been through a bit together.
Do you have a map of the Sea of Devils ?
I don't have one.
But if Brother Wang wants one,
you can go to the treasure pavilions in the cities.
You might have some luck there.
Then Brother Qiu should come with me to the city.
We'll buy a map together.
You can chase them after I obtain a map.
He has forced me into a situation where I need to kill them
but he's blocking me.
Now that I'm in this situation,
I can't wait,
I can only comply.
That's truly a great scheme...
All my knowledge of the Sea of Devils
from all the years I have traveled
is compiled in this jade.
There might be some mistakes,
but not too many.
Brother Wang,
If there's nothing else,
I'm leaving.
Thank you.
You're not going to check it ?
Do I need to ?
Brother Wang,
I wouldn't give you false information.
You can rest assured.
I need to gather multiple maps
to cross reference them
and find out the real information.
7 days later
There are so many mutants in the Sea of Devils,
yet this guy is just strolling around.
How long until we reach Lian Mo City ?
Something's wrong here.
I don't hear any sound.
Underworld Ice Flame,
emerge !
The beast hiding in this mountain
can take a humanoid shape ?
Interesting...
Although the beast isn't strong,
I can help it cultivate to grow in strength.
Break !
A mosquito beast ?
Tu Si was almost killed by their encirclement before...
This one must be of the same race.
I am here !
What the hell is this ?
Why is it even uglier than the ape ?
This new devil seems dumb.
I'll let him do the dirty work.
If it turns out he's useless
I'll just clean up after him.
Such speed !
So powerful !
If it weren't for this stupid ape,
I wouldn't have come out to look for trouble.
So it's hard huh ?
I want to see how he will capture this thing.
Split !
Illusion !
So it will fight itself.
Master always has good ideas !
It seems that it can not just attack with its dart,
but it can also attack with its mouth.
You cannot run away !
Master is getting more and more terrifying...
Ridiculous.
Master, you are too generous !
You've given him too many treasures to absorb !
Let's go.
How about 3 mid quality spirit stones ?
I can't go cheaper.
Let's talk later.
Lian Mo City\NSea of Devils
Long time no see, fellow cultivator.
The Sea isn't very calm lately.
This is a special item...
These artifacts are made from middle grade Spirit Beast bones.
Especially this bell,
it was made out of beast ear drums and wings.
It is extraordinary.
I exchange for spirit stones.
I want the bell, for 30 spirit stones ?
Sold.
Next person.
This crystal furnace
can be exchanged for high grade pills.
I am looking for secret cultivation techniques !
I have a book about the secret water sealing pills.
This gourd can transmit the voice,
I sell it for 100 spirit stones.
Among all those items
maybe one can sell for a high price.
Fellow cultivator, I'm in !
It turns there are many strong people hidden here.
Fellow Daoist, don't compete with me !
Next person.
I will trade sea beast cores for a map of ancient teleportation formations,
the more complete, the better.
Little friend,
this kind of high quality map is invaluable in the Sea of Devils.
It will cost 1000 high quality spirit stones
plus some of your items, it might be difficult for you.
A thousand ?
Who has this much ?
Yeah right ?
Then I'll offer a top grade spirit stone.
Does anyone have a map ?
Top quality ?!
I heard it wrong.
A top quality spirit stone...
No way !
Aren't they extinct ?
Is this a top quality spirit stone ?
Unfortunately I don't have a map...
Next person.
Fellow cultivator,
I have what you're looking for.
But with the top quality spirit stone,
I want one more thing in exchange.
First, the map.
This map not only records the teleportation formations
but also how damaged they are.
What else do you need ?
I want you to kill someone.
What cultivation level ?
Peak Late stage Nascent Soul,
Half-Step Soul Formation.
Lead the way.
Fellow cultivator,
this person is nearby.
You will lay in ambush.
When I invite him out,
you attack.
What's wrong ?
You bastard !
I'll kill you !
You can all come out.
When did you find out ?
When we arrived here.
You are smart.
But it's too late.
This place is too remote
so no one can help you.
You are...
Go together, kill him !
This sword sheath is exactly the same as the one I used in the past.
Is there more of these ?
It has a strong killing intent.
The energy is sealed in the sheath.
If I push the sword a third of the way in
it can release this much energy.
If I can sheathe it entirely...
Its strength will be tremendous.
Spot on.
Take this, and this,
and this spiced beef, take all of it !
outstanding form and spirit.
Blood for blood.
I will wipe out your Wang Family
to avenge my grandson Teng Li !
Wang Lin,
look how kind I am !
I let you reunite with your parents...
I have waited for this day
for 400 years.
Zhao...
I'm coming back !
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.